<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blog on ★✰ Aditya Agarwal ★✰ </title>
    <link>https://artsofbaniya.com/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blog on ★✰ Aditya Agarwal ★✰ </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 19:28:20 -0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://artsofbaniya.com/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Top 5 Learnings After 2 Years of Being a Founder</title>
      <link>https://artsofbaniya.com/blog/top-5-learnings-after-2-years-of-being-a-founder/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 19:28:20 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://artsofbaniya.com/blog/top-5-learnings-after-2-years-of-being-a-founder/</guid>
      <description>I shut down my first company in Oct’21. We were building first, unprepared, listening to folks who weren’t our ideal customers and investors. The core things learned retrospectively:
Sell first, build later: Focus on building accurate user personas first. And talking to sufficient users before building anything. Be Patient: Things take time to pan out. Once you actually zero down on the building, it could take 6-12 months to see the impact and meaningful adoption.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Side Hustling Since 8 Years</title>
      <link>https://artsofbaniya.com/blog/side-hustling-since-8-years/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 19:27:22 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://artsofbaniya.com/blog/side-hustling-since-8-years/</guid>
      <description>In Noida, India, a well-fed kid from a middle-class working family with strict focus on education and nothing else, I&amp;rsquo;m not entirely how the desire to earn money kicks in.
Finance of a Kid Pocket Money: At this point I had ₹1/day as pocket my money.
Cost of Snacks:
A lays packet (or cheetos, my favorite was ₹10). A small coke or pepsi bottle was ₹7. A snack item was ₹7-10, while a fancier dish in the school canteen would be ₹20-25 Side Hustles 8 years old, My first earning: ₹120 Two friends and I, the three musketeers, setup a games stall at a local community event, that got me my first ₹150.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
