<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>About on ★✰ Aditya Agarwal ★✰ </title>
    <link>https://blog.artsofbaniya.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content in About on ★✰ Aditya Agarwal ★✰ </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 19:28:20 -0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.artsofbaniya.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Top 5 Learnings After 2 Years of Being a Founder</title>
      <link>https://blog.artsofbaniya.com/blog/top-5-learnings-after-2-years-of-being-a-founder/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 19:28:20 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.artsofbaniya.com/blog/top-5-learnings-after-2-years-of-being-a-founder/</guid>
      <description>I shut down my first company in Oct’21. We were building first, unprepared, listening to folks who weren’t our ideal customers and investors. The core things learned retrospectively:
Sell first, build later: Focus on building accurate user personas first. And talking to sufficient users before building anything. Be Patient: Things take time to pan out. Once you actually zero down on the building, it could take 6-12 months to see the impact and meaningful adoption.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Side Hustling Since 8 Years</title>
      <link>https://blog.artsofbaniya.com/blog/side-hustling-since-8-years/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 19:27:22 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.artsofbaniya.com/blog/side-hustling-since-8-years/</guid>
      <description>This is a page about »Side Hustling Since 8 Years«.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Books</title>
      <link>https://blog.artsofbaniya.com/books/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.artsofbaniya.com/books/</guid>
      <description>Books most impactful in my early-stage Tech founder journey
Getting the right Founder Mindset Startup CEO : A Field Guide to Scaling your Busines The otherside of Innovation : Solving the Execution Challenge (Harvard Business Review) What Customers Want : Using Outcome-Driven Innovation The Mom&amp;#39;s Test : How to Talk to Customers Who Not How : The Formula to Achieve Bigger Goals Through Accelerating Teamwork Networking &amp;amp; Sales It&amp;#39;s Not All About Me : The Top Ten Techniques for Building Quick Rapport with Anyone To Sell is Human : The Surprising Truth About Movin Others Challenger Sale : Taking Control of the Customer Conversation Productivity Predictably Irrational - Dan Ariely Eat that frog : 21 Great Ways to Stop Procrastinating Innovation to Create Breakthrough Products and Services Deep Work : Rules of Focused Success in a Distracted World Venture Deals Other Resources: Product Management Resourced by product folks Blog&amp;#39;s On FirstRound HackerNews </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
